Register of the Ernest Lundeen Papers, 1860-1944
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1894-1942
  - 1937-1940. Constituent mail, congressional office business and letters to organizations arranged alphabetically
    - Post Office Department
      - Pollock (Folder 44)
      - Preston (Folder 45)
      - Princeton (Folder 46)
      - Randolph (Folder 47)
      - Remer (Folder 48)
      - Richfield (Folder 49)
      - Robbinsdale (Folder 50)
      - Rock Creek (Folder 51)
      - Roseau (Folder 52)
      - Roseland (Folder 53)
      - Rush City (Folder 54)
      - Rushford (Folder 55)
      - Russell (Folder 56)
      - St. Charles (Folder 57)
      - St. Paul (Folder 58)
      - Seaforth (Folder 59)
      - Sedan (Folder 60)
      - Shevlin (Folder 61)
      - Stephen (Folder 62)
      - Stillwater (Folder 63)
      - Syre (Folder 64)
      - Thief River Falls (Box 214., Folder 1)
      - Thomson (Folder 2)
      - Underwood (Folder 3)
      - Utica (Folder 4)
      - Vernon Center (Folder 5)
      - Wadena (Folder 6)
      - Webster (Folder 7)
      - Willmar (Folder 8)
      - Winger (Folder 9)
      - Worthington (Folder 10)
      - Wyoming (Folder 11)
      - Zim (Folder 12)
      - Zimmerman (Folder 13)
      - Zumbrota (Folder 14)
      - Clerks (Folder 15)
      - Discontinue Saturday night mail cars (Folder 16)
      - Laborers (Folder 17)
      - Postmasters (Folder 18)
    - Potter, Thomas John (Folder 19)
    - Poulos, James P. (Folder 20)
    - Poultry Congress (Folder 21)
    - Public Ownership League of America (Folder 22)
    - Public Works Administration (Folder 23)
    - Publication requests (Folder 24)
    - Purple Heart, Military Order of the (Folder 25)
    - Putman, Jack D. (Folder 26)
    - Putzier, Robert A. (Folder 27)
    - Quarnstrom, Milton (Folder 28)
    - Quigley, Herbert Anthony (Folder 29)
    - Quinlan, Elizabeth (Folder 30)
    - R personal (Folder 31)
    - R unsorted (Folder 32)
    - Radio stations
      - Mankato (Box 215., Folder 1)
      - Minneapolis (Folder 2)
      - Red Wing (Folder 3)
      - St. Cloud (Folder 4)
      - St. Paul (Folder 5)
    - Radke Oil Company (Folder 6)
    - Railroad Brotherhoods
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Legislative Board (Folder 8)
    - Railway employees (Folder 9)
    - Railway Mail Association (Folder 10)
    - Randall, E. W., Mrs. (Folder 11)
    - Randall, Edwin T. (Folder 12)
    - Rasmussen, Paul (Folder 13)
    - Rathmann, H. W. (Folder 14)
    - Reedholm, Mildred (Folder 15)
    - Reemployment Service (Folder 16)
    - Regular Veterans Association (Folder 17)
    - Reilly, Lawrence F. (Folder 18)
    - Reimers, Fred (Folder 19)
    - Riddle, Jesse H. (Folder 20)
    - Riggs, John E. (Folder 21)
    - Riley, Jim (Folder 22)
    - Roberts, Fred C. (Folder 23)
    - Robinson Plumbing Supply Company (Folder 24)
    - Rogalla, Ralph (Folder 25)
    - Rolfson, Ollie B. (Folder 26)
    - Rosenberg, Hugo, Mr. and Mrs. (Folder 27)
    - Ross, Fred C. (Folder 28)
    - Rousselange, Peter (Folder 29)
    - Roy, L. E. (Folder 30)
    - Rural Electrification Association (Folder 31)
    - Ryser, Fred (Folder 32)
    - S personal (Folder 33)
    - S unsorted (Box 216., Folder 1)
    - Sabesewitz, Harry (Folder 2)
    - Sackriasson, Kate (Folder 3)
    - St. Anthony and Dakota Elevator Company (Folder 4)
    - St. Croix Parks Project (Folder 5)
    - St. Olaf College (Folder 6)
    - St. Paul Association of Commerce (Folder 7)
    - St. Paul Trades and Labor Assembly (Folder 8)
    - Sanders, Fred (Folder 9)
    - Sanderson, S. O. (Folder 10)
    - Satterlund, Andrew (Folder 11)
    - Saturday Lunch Club (Folder 12)
    - Savage, Hazel, Mrs. (Folder 13)
    - Schacht, Edward R. (Folder 14)
    - Schaefer, John Jacob (Folder 15)
    - Schneiner, Isedor (Folder 16)
    - Schilplin, Fred (Folder 17)
    - Schlick, Paul F. (Folder 18)
    - Schnedler, Louis H. (Folder 19)
    - Schwartz, Sam (Folder 20)
    - Scroggin, Arthur E. (Folder 21)
    - Seaburg, Emil (Folder 22)
    - Seibel, John (Folder 23)
    - Shaffer, John W. (Folder 24)
    - Sherman, Elmer (Folder 25)
    - Shidler, Julia, Mrs. (Folder 26)
    - Shipton, Harold H. (Folder 27)
    - Solberg, K. K. (Folder 28)
    - Stern, Robert (Folder 29)
    - Subscriptions
      - General, daily papers (Folder 30)
      - General, Minnesota papers (Folder 31)
      - General, opinion papers (Folder 32)
      - General for the office (Folder 33)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 34)
      - A (Folder 35)
      - B (Folder 36)
      - C (Folder 37)
      - D (Folder 38)
      - F (Box 217., Folder 1)
      - H (Folder 2)
      - L (Folder 3)
      - M (Folder 4)
      - N (Folder 5)
      - P (Folder 6)
      - R (Folder 7)
      - S (Folder 8)
      - T (Folder 9)
      - U (Folder 10)
      - V (Folder 11)
      - W (Folder 12)
    - Sullivan, George (Folder 13)
    - Sweger, John W. (Folder 14)
    - Syverson, Ruth Standal (Folder 15)
    - T personal (Folder 16)
    - T unsorted (Folder 17)
    - Templin, Ann, Emma, and Helen (Folder 18)
    - Thank you letters (Folder 19)
    - Thompson, William Hale (Folder 20)
    - Thompson's Dairy (Folder 21)
    - Thomson, H. R. (Folder 22)
    - U personal (Folder 23)
    - U unsorted (Folder 24)
    - Ugeblad Publishing Company (Folder 25)
    - Ulrick, Henry F. (Folder 26)
    - Union Party, Minnesota. See also Box 208, Holmes, Emil (Box 218., Folder 1)
    - The Unionist (Folder 2)
    - United Automobile Workers of America (Folder 3)
    - United Federal Workers of America (Folder 4)
    - United States Air Conditioning Corporation (Folder 5)
    - United States Weather Bureau (Folder 6)
    - University of Minnesota (Folder 7)
    - Upper Mississippi Waterway Association (Folder 8)
    - Urdl, Augustus (Folder 9)
    - V personal (Folder 10)
    - V unsorted (Folder 11)
    - Vaala, Alfred T. (Folder 12)
    - Van Kleeck, Mary (Folder 13)
    - Vercoe, W. S. (Folder 14)
    - Veterans Administration
      - General (Folder 15)
      - Minneapolis (complaints against) (Folder 16)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Folder 17)
    - W personal (Folder 18)
    - W unsorted (Folder 19)
    - Wacholz, E. F. (Folder 20)
    - Wage scales
      - Red Wing Dam (Folder 21)
      - St. Cloud Post Office (Folder 22)
      - St. Cloud Veterans Association (Folder 23)
      - Sanitary districts (Folder 24)
    - War Department (Folder 25)
    - Warden, John B. (Folder 26)
    - Williams, Howard Y. (Folder 27)
    - Woodward & Lathrop (Folder 28)
    - Youngdahl, Emil (Folder 29)
- SUBJECT FILE, 1906-1942
  - General (Box 219., Folder 1-3)
  - Accidents
    - General (Box 220., Folder 1)
    - Highway (Folder 2)
  - Agriculture (Folder 3)
  - Aid to Allies (Folder 4)
  - Alaska (Folder 5)
  - Aliens (Folder 6)
  - Alsace-Lorraine (Folder 7)
  - America (Folder 8)
  - American Civil Liberties Union
    - To 1936 (Folder 9)
    - 1936-1940 (Folder 10)
  - American Enterprise Association (Folder 11)
  - American Labor party (Folder 12)
  - American League Against War and Fascism (Folder 13)
  - American League for Peace and Democracy (Folder 14)
  - American Legion (Box 221., Folder 1)
  - American Liberty League (Folder 2)
  - Ameringer, Oscar (Folder 3)
  - Amlie, Thomas R. (Folder 4)
  - Anderson, William A. (Folder 5)
  - Andrew, A. Piatt (Folder 6)
  - Antarctic (Folder 7)
  - Anti-lynching bill (Folder 8)
  - Anti-trust laws (Folder 9)
  - Archer Daniels Midland Company (Folder 10)
  - Argentine (Folder 11)
  - Army
    - European nations (Folder 12)
    - U.S.
      - To 1936 (Folder 13-14)
      - 1936-1940 (Box 222., Folder 1)
  - Army and Navy appropriations (Folder 2)
  - Army and Navy Club (Folder 3)
  - Astor, Nancy L. (Folder 4)
  - Austria (Folder 5)
  - Aviation
    - General
      - To 1936 (Folder 6)
      - 1936-1940 (Folder 7-9)
    - Air Line Pilots Association (Box 223., Folder 1)
    - Berg, Ernest (Folder 2)
    - Civil Aeronautics Authority (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Folder 4)
    - Earhart, Amelia (Folder 5)
    - Legislation (Folder 6)
    - Lighter than air craft (Folder 7)
    - Military (Folder 8)
    - Northwest Airlines (Box 224., Folder 1)
    - Pan American Airways (Folder 2)
    - C. E. Rosendahl's book draft and articles (Folder 3)
    - Speech material (Folder 4)
    - U.S. Navy (Folder 5)
  - Baer, John (Folder 6)
  - Banking
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Commercial credit (Folder 8)
  - Bankruptcy (Folder 9)
  - Battle of life (Folder 10)
  - Belgium (Folder 11)
  - Bell, Robert C., Jr. (Folder 12)
  - Bellamy, Edward (Folder 13)
  - Benson, Elmer (Folder 14)
  - Berger, Victor L. (Folder 15)
  - Billings, Warren K. (Folder 16)
  - Binderup, Charles E. (Folder 17)
  - Birth control (Box 225., Folder 1)
  - Black Tom case (Folder 2)
  - Bloom, Saul (Folder 3)
  - Bonus for military (Folder 4)
  - Boscoe, John (Folder 5)
  - Bottomley, Horatio (Folder 6)
  - Boyle, William S. (Folder 7)
  - Brazil (Folder 8)
  - Bridges, Harry (Folder 9)
  - Brittain, Vera (personal letter to Peace-Lovers) (Folder 10)
  - Brookwood Labor College (Folder 11)
  - Bryan, William Jennings (Folder 12)
  - Budget, U.S.
    - General (Folder 13)
    - Budget Bureau (Folder 14)
  - Bund investigation (Folder 15)
  - Burke-Wadsworth bill (Folder 16)
  - Burnquist, J. A. A. (Folder 17)
  - Business
    - General (Folder 18)
    - Monopoly (Folder 19)
    - Tax Research Institute of America Reports (Box 226., Folder 1)
    - Trends (Folder 2)
  - California (Folder 3)
  - Canada (Folder 4)
  - Canal
    - Florida (Folder 5)
    - Nicaragua (Folder 6)
    - St. Lawrence (Folder 7)
  - Capital punishment (Folder 8)
  - Carnegie, Andrew (Folder 9)
  - Cash (Folder 10)
  - Catholics (Folder 11)
  - Edith Cavell School, Minneapolis, Minnesota (Folder 12)
  - Chain stores (Folder 13)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (Folder 14)
  - Chamber of Commerce of the United States (Box 227., Folder 1)
  - Child labor (Folder 2)
  - China (Folder 3)
  - Christgau, Victor (Folder 4)
  - Christianson, Theodore (Folder 5)
  - Civil rights (Folder 6)
  - Civil Service (Folder 7)
  - Class struggle (Folder 8)
  - Clippings (items of interest to Lundeen from newspapers, periodicals, etc.) (Folder 9)
    - 1935 March-April (Folder 10)
    - 1939
      - August (Folder 11)
      - September (Folder 12)
      - October (Folder 13)
      - November (Folder 14)
      - December (Folder 15)
    - 1940
      - January (Folder 16)
      - February (Box 228., Folder 1)
      - March (Folder 2)
      - April (Folder 3)
      - May (Folder 4)
      - July (Folder 5)
      - August (Folder 6)
  - Coal (Folder 7)
  - Colorado River (Folder 8)
  - Columbia River region (Folder 9)
  - Commercial clubs (Folder 10)
  - Committee for the Nation (Folder 11-13)
  - Communism
    - General (Box 229., Folder 1-2)
    - Marx, Karl (Folder 3)
    - Minnesota (Folder 4)
    - Young Communist League (Folder 5)
  - Congress, U.S.
    - 1937 (Folder 6)
    - 1938 (Folder 7)
    - 1939 (Folder 8)
    - 1940 (Folder 9)
  - Congressmen (Folder 10)
  - Conscription
    - To 1936 (Folder 11)
    - 1936-1940 (Box 230., Folder 1-2)
    - Bibliography (Folder 3)
    - Lundeen statements (Folder 4)
    - Minnesota editorials (Folder 5)
    - Other countries (Folder 6)
  - Conservation (Folder 7)
  - The Constitution (Folder 8)
  - Constitutional rights (Folder 9)
  - Continental Congress of Farmers and Workers (Folder 10)
  - Consumers (Folder 11)
  - Cooperatives
    - General (Box 231., Folder 1)
    - College (Folder 2)
    - Foreign (Folder 3)
    - Minnesota (Folder 4)
  - Corporations (Folder 5)
  - Cost of living (Folder 6)
  - Cost of production (Folder 7)
  - Cotton (Folder 8)
  - Coughlin, Charles E. (Folder 9)
  - Courts (Folder 10)
  - Crime (Box 232., Folder 1)
  - Crops
    - General (Folder 2)
    - Insurance (Folder 3)
  - Cuba (Folder 4)
  - Czechoslovakia (Folder 5)
  - Dairy surpluses (Folder 6)
  - Dams
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Bonneville (Folder 8)
    - Grand Coulee (Folder 9)
  - Daughters of the American Revolution (Folder 10)
  - Davis, Tom (Folder 11)
  - Dawes, Charles G. (Folder 12)
  - Death and damage law (Folder 13)
  - Debt, U.S. (Folder 14)
  - Debts, World War I
    - General, 1922-1940 (Box 233., Folder 1-2)
    - Bibliography (Folder 3)
    - Cancellation (Folder 4)
    - Congressional resolutions and bills (Folder 5)
    - Estonia (Folder 6)
    - Finland (Folder 7)
    - France (Folder 8)
    - Great Britain (Folder 9)
    - Hungary (Box 234., Folder 1)
    - Interest on (Folder 2)
    - Loans to foreign countries (Folder 3)
    - Make Europe Pay War Debts Committee (formerly the Islands for War Debts Committee)
      - General (Folder 4)
      - Granik Forum, 1940 August 19 (Folder 5)
      - Press comments (Folder 6)
      - Publicity (Folder 7)
      - Moratorium (Folder 8)
    - Romania (Folder 9)
    - Speech material (Folder 10)
    - Statements by Lundeen (Folder 11)
    - Uncollected (Folder 12)
  - Deficiency judgements (Folder 13)
  - Delaney, Patrick (Folder 14)
  - Democracy (Folder 15)
  - Democratic Party, Minnesota (Box 235., Folder 1)
  - Democratic Party, National (Folder 2)
  - Denmark (Folder 3)
  - Depression (Folder 4)
  - Dies Committee (Folder 5)
  - Diesel engines (Folder 6)
  - District of Columbia (Folder 7)
  - Dominican Republic (Folder 8)
  - Drought (Folder 9)
  - Earle, George H. (Folder 10)
  - Eberhardt, Adolph (Folder 11)
  - Economy
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Economic reports (Folder 13)
    - Policy (Box 236., Folder 1)
  - Editorials (Folder 2)
  - Education
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Minnesota (Folder 4)
    - Sex education (Folder 5)
    - Teachers (Folder 6)
  - Election 1938 (Folder 7)
  - Election laws (Folder 8)
  - Election results, 1922-1928 (Folder 9)
  - Election results, 1936, Minneapolis (Folder 10)
  - Eliot, George Fielding (Box 237., Folder 1)
  - Embargo
    - General background material, 1933-1940 (Folder 2-4)
    - Herbert Hoover's statements (Folder 5)
    - House of Representatives vote, 1939 November 3 (Folder 6)
    - Labor stand (Folder 7)
    - Lundeen statements (Folder 8)
  - Embargoes, U.S. (Folder 9)
  - Emergency Railroad Transportation Act of 1933-1934 (Folder 10)
  - Enlistment, Voluntary (Folder 11)
  - Equal rights (Women's rights) (Folder 12)
  - Erickson, Lief (Box 238., Folder 1)
  - Esch-Cummins Law (Folder 2)
  - Export-Import Bank (Folder 3)
  - Exports (Folder 4)
  - Famine (Folder 5)
  - Farm bill (Folder 6)
  - Farm Bureau Federation, American (Folder 7)
  - Farm Credit Administration (Folder 8)
  - Farm parity (Folder 9)
  - Farm relief
    - General (Folder 10)
    - Minnesota (Folder 11)
  - Farmer Labor Clubs (Folder 12)
  - Farmer Labor Federation (political) (Folder 13)
  - Farmer Labor Party
    - Undated (Folder 14)
    - General (Box 239., Folder 1)
    - 1918 (Folder 2)
    - 1920 (Folder 3)
    - 1922 (Folder 4)
    - 1924 (Folder 5)
    - 1925 (Folder 6)
    - 1926 (Folder 7)
    - 1927 (Folder 8)
    - 1928
      - General (Folder 9)
      - Convention, Faribault, Minnesota, May 7 (Folder 10)
      - Radio campaign (Folder 11)
    - 1928-1929 election results (Folder 12)
    - 1929 (Folder 13)
    - 1930 (Folder 14)
    - 1931 (Box 240., Folder 1)
    - 1932 (Folder 2)
    - 1933 (Folder 3)
    - 1934 (Folder 4)
    - 1935 (Folder 5)
    - 1936 (Folder 6)
    - 1937 (Folder 7)
    - 1938
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Bergquist, George Wilton, The Farmer Labor Movement in Minnesota. Typescript (Folder 9)
      - Minnesota reorganization (Folder 10)
    - 1939 (Folder 11)
    - 1940
      - General (Folder 12)
      - Convention, March (Folder 13)
    - Clipping service (Box 241., Folder 1-2)
    - Educational Bureau (Folder 3)
    - History (Folder 4)
    - Leaders
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Bennett, James R. (Folder 6)
      - Brobeck, George K. (Folder 7)
      - Connery, William P. (Folder 8)
      - Dickson, James (Folder 9)
      - Ferch, Michael (Folder 10)
      - Fritsche, L. A. (Folder 11)
      - Gegner, George (Box 242., Folder 1)
      - Green, William (Folder 2)
      - Hill, Knute (Folder 3)
      - Johnson, Dewey (Folder 4)
      - Keesy, Truman J. (Folder 5)
      - Kennedy, Jesse T. (Folder 6)
      - Kvale, Paul John (Folder 7)
      - La Follette, Philip (Folder 8)
      - La Follette, Robert M. (Folder 9)
      - Lemke, William (Folder 10)
      - Lewis, John L. (Folder 11)
      - Luehrs, Henry F. (Folder 12)
      - Mandel, Benjamin (Folder 13)
      - Maverick, Maury (Folder 14)
      - Mudge, Rollo (Folder 15)
      - Parsons, Frank (Folder 16)
      - Peterson, Harold L. (Folder 17)
      - Rankin, John (Folder 18)
      - Teigan, Henry (Folder 19)
      - Thomas, Norman (Folder 20)
      - Voorhis, Jerry (Folder 21)
      - Webb, Frank Elbridge (Folder 22)
      - Wheeler, Burton K. (Box 243., Folder 1)
      - Williams, Howard Y. (Folder 2)
    - National
      - General
        - General (Folder 3-4)
        - Labor (Folder 5)
        - Mailing lists (Folder 6)
      - Alabama (Folder 7)
      - Arizona (Folder 8)
      - Arkansas (Folder 9)
      - California (Folder 10)
      - Colorado (Folder 11)
      - Connecticut (Box 244., Folder 1)
      - Delaware (Folder 2)
      - Florida (Folder 3)
      - Hawaii (Folder 4)
      - Illinois (Folder 5)
      - Indiana (Folder 6)
      - Iowa (Folder 7)
      - Kansas (Folder 8)
      - Kentucky (Folder 9)
      - Louisiana (Folder 10)
      - Maine (Folder 11)
      - Maryland (Folder 12)
      - Massachusetts (Folder 13)
      - Michigan (Folder 14)
      - Minnesota (Folder 15-16)
      - Minnesota (Box 245., Folder 1-2)
      - Missouri (Folder 3)
      - Montana (Folder 4)
      - Nebraska (Folder 5)
      - Nevada (Folder 6)
      - New Jersey (Folder 7)
      - New York (Folder 8)
      - North Dakota (Folder 9)
      - Ohio (Folder 10)
      - Oklahoma (Folder 11)
      - Oregon (Folder 12)
      - Pennsylvania (Folder 13)
      - Rhode Island (Folder 14)
      - South Dakota (Folder 15)
      - Tennessee (Folder 16)
      - Texas (Folder 17)
      - Virginia (Folder 18)
      - Washington (Folder 19)
      - Washington, D. C. (Box 246., Folder 1)
      - Wisconsin (Folder 2)
      - Wyoming (Folder 3)
      - Canada (Folder 4)
      - Allied organizations
        - General (Folder 5)
        - American Labor Party (Folder 6)
        - American Newspaper Guild (Folder 7)
        - Continental Congress of Farmers and Workers (Folder 8)
        - Farmer-Labor Association of Minnesota (Folder 9)
        - Free Economy League (Folder 10)
        - Labor Party (Folder 11)
        - League for Industrial Democracy (Folder 12)
        - League of War Veteran Guardsmen (Box 247., Folder 1)
        - Liberty Party (Folder 2)
        - National Farmers Union (Folder 3)
        - National Popular Government League (Folder 4)
        - National Unemployment League (Folder 5)
        - Non-Partisan League (Folder 6)
        - People's Lobby (Folder 7)
        - Plain Talk (Folder 8)
        - Progressive Party (Folder 9)
        - Prohibition Party (Folder 10)
        - Townsend bill backers (Folder 11)
      - Production (Folder 12)
      - Service Bureau (Folder 13)
      - Speech invitations (Folder 14)
      - Tax evasion (H. Fitterman) (Folder 15)
      - Third party (Folder 16)
      - Veterans (Box 248., Folder 1)
      - Woman's Forum, The (Folder 2)
      - Women's Federation (Folder 3)
      - Youth (Folder 4)
  - Farmers
    - Migration (Folder 5)
    - Unions (Folder 6)
  - Farmers Holiday Association, National (Folder 7)
  - Farmers Washington Service (Folder 8)
  - Farms
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Labor supply (Folder 10)
    - Loans (Folder 11)
    - Mortgages (Folder 12)
  - Fascism (Box 249., Folder 1)
  - Federal agencies - Chief legal officers (Folder 2)
  - Federal employees (Folder 3)
  - Federal Reserve Bank (Folder 4)
  - Federal Trade Commission (Folder 5)
  - Feminism (Folder 6)
  - Fifth column (Folder 7)
  - Films (block booking) (Folder 8)
  - Finance
    - General (Folder 9)
    - Depression (Folder 10)
    - Economy and banking system (Folder 11)
  - Finland
    - General (Folder 12)
    - Aid for (Folder 13)
  - Fires (Box 250., Folder 1)
  - "The Fishes of the Klamath Basin," Gilbert H. Charles (Folder 2)
  - Flag, U.S. (Folder 3)
  - Fleming, Philip (Folder 4)
  - Flood control (Folder 5)
  - Food stamp plan (Folder 6)
  - Ford, Guy Stanton (Folder 7)
  - Ford, Henry (Folder 8)
  - Foreign decorations (Folder 9)
  - Foreign policy
    - General (Folder 10-11)
    - General (Box 251., Folder 1-2)
    - Aggression (Folder 3)
    - Aid to Allies
      - General (Folder 4-5)
      - General (Box 252., Folder 1)
      - Exports (Folder 2)
      - Johnson Act (Folder 3)
      - Legislation (Folder 4)
      - Lundeen statements (Folder 5)
      - Opposition to (Folder 6)
    - Balkans (Folder 7)
    - Collective security (Folder 8)
    - Committee on Military Affairs
      - "Frontier on the Rhine" clippings (Folder 9)
      - "Frontier on the Rhine" speech draft (Folder 10)
    - Economic union (Folder 11)
    - Hull, Cordell (Folder 12)
    - Jackson, Andrew (Folder 13)
    - Lundeen speech draft, "Keep Out of War..." (Folder 14)
    - Lundeen speech material (Folder 15)
    - Neutrality
      - General (Box 253., Folder 1-3)
      - British interpretation (Folder 4)
      - Laws (Folder 5)
      - Pro and con (Folder 6)
      - Proclamation, 1939 September 5 (Box 254., Folder 1)
      - "Whose War Is It?", by Earl Browder (Folder 2)
      - Neutrality Act, 1939 (Folder 3)
      - Neutrality petitions, 1939 January (Folder 4)
      - Neutrality zone (Folder 5)
      - "Social Justice" article material (Folder 6)
      - Soviet Union (Folder 7)
      - Welles, Sumner (Folder 8)
  - Foreign Relations Committee (Folder 9)
  - 4 H clubs (Folder 10)
  - France
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Graves for American soldiers (Folder 12)
  - Franchise, Washington, D.C. (Folder 13)
  - Frank, Glenn (Folder 14)
  - Free speech (Folder 15)
  - Fuel (Box 255., Folder 1)
  - Gallagher, Thomas (Folder 2)
  - Gannett, Frank (Folder 3)
  - General Drivers Union (Folder 4)
  - General Welfare Act (Folder 5)
  - Germans in America (Folder 6)
  - Germany
    - General (Folder 7-8)
    - Graf Spee (Folder 9)
    - Hitler, Adolf (Folder 10)
    - League Against Fascism (Folder 11)
    - Military theory (Folder 12)
    - Persecutions (Folder 13)
    - Propaganda (Folder 14)
    - Resources (Folder 15)
    - Social policy (Folder 16)
    - Soviet Union relations (Box 256., Folder 1)
    - U.S. relations (Folder 2)
  - Gilbert, A. B. (Folder 3)
  - Gold (Folder 4)
  - Goverment administration (Folder 5)
  - Grange
    - Minnesota (Folder 6)
    - National (Folder 7)
  - Grasshoppers (Folder 8)
  - Great Britain
    - General (Folder 9-10)
    - Anti-British feeling (Folder 11)
    - Churchill, Winston (Folder 12)
    - Defense (Folder 13)
    - Diplomats (Box 257., Folder 1)
    - Foreign policy (Folder 2)
    - George VI, King, and Queen Elizabeth (Folder 3)
    - Labor and the war (Folder 4)
    - Loans (Folder 5)
    - Possessions (Folder 6)
    - Propaganda (Folder 7)
    - Supplies purchased from the U.S. (Folder 8)
    - War
      - Aims (Folder 9)
      - Budget (Folder 10)
      - Shipping (Folder 11)
  - Greece (Box 258., Folder 1)
  - Greenbelt community (Folder 2)
  - Greenland
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Lundeen statements (Folder 4)
  - Guam (Folder 5)
  - Guffey, Joseph F. (Folder 6)
  - Gude Brothers (Folder 7)
  - Ham and Eggs (Folder 8)
  - Hansen, Ferdinand (Folder 9)
  - Hatch Act (Folder 10)
  - Hawaii
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Kalaniananole, Jonah (Folder 12)
    - Statehood (Folder 13)
  - Haycraft, Kenneth C. (Box 259., Folder 1)
  - Health (Folder 2-3)
  - Hearst, William R. (Folder 4)
  - Highways (Folder 5)
  - Hoan, Daniel (Folder 6)